本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 闲鱼
校对： 闲鱼  后期： 小安
- 所有人都到后面来 厨房 - 什么?
- Everyone in the back, into the kitchen. - Excuse me?
- 快点 别磨蹭  - 哦 好的
- Let's go, move! - Ok, all right.
加齐先生 我本来要打电话的
Mr. Gazi, I was just about to call you.
我和雷曼说了 他说我还有时间
I talked to Raman, he said I have more time.
他可不是这么告诉我的
That's not what he told me.
他说我应该来着动动筋骨
He said I should come and break some bones.
等一下 等一下 等一下
Wait, wait, wait.
等等 等等 不 等等
Hold on, hold on, no! Wait!
求你了 别这样 求你了
C'mon, don't do this. Please.
淡定 别
Calm down, just...
你们真的没必要这么做 好吗?
You don't have to do this, all right?
我能把钱给你 再给我一天时间
I can get you the money. Just give me one more day.
卧底游戏 第一季 第六集
- 跑得还好吗? - 天啊!
- Good run? - Jesus!
你吓死我了
You scared the hell out of me.
你知道要进来多么容易吗?
You have any idea how easy it is to get in here?
你至少应该学会锁门啊
You should try locking your door for starters.
是啊 是啊
Yeah, yeah.
出什么事儿了?
What's going on?
丽贝卡打电话开会
Rebecca called an early briefing.
你没接电话 所以我就自己来了
You weren't picking up so... I decided to come by.
你考虑要添置点家具什么的吗?
You thinking about putting some furniture in this place?
有用的都在这了
I got the important stuff.
你搬进来多久了 四个月?
How long have you been here, four months?
- 六个半月  - 六个半月了?
- Six and a half. - Six and a half months?
你养了盆花 还把它养死了
And you have one plant, and you killed it.
看看吧 活脱脱一个你啊
Look at that. Look, it's a metaphor.
离婚了也不用把自己弄得像懒汉一样啊
Just because you're divorced doesn't mean you have to live like a slob.
分居 好吗? 不一样的
Separated. All right? There's a big difference.
好吧 约翰 我只是想说
All right. I'm just saying, John.
这不是家 让人憋屈死了
This isn't a home, it's depressing.
艾米丽住这吗? 她睡哪 ?
Does Emily stay here? Where... where does she sleep?
好了 别说了行吗
Alright. That's enough, okay.
我去冲个澡
I'm going to have a shower.
- 如果愿意 给自己来杯咖啡 - 好吧
- Make yourself some coffee, if you want. - All right.
- 嘿 快看啊 -那是谁啊?
- Hey, look at this. - Who's that?
他都和她侃了二十分钟了
He's been cracking her up for the last twenty minutes.
你知道那人是谁吗?
You have any idea who that guy is?
不知道
None.
他们被指向了你 所以
...they're pointed at you, so...
我只记得你当时是个没用的醉鬼
All I remember is you were a sloppy drunk.
我当时是醉的不轻
I was an exceptional drunk.
哦 好的 我想起来了
Oh. Okay, I remember it.
记得你 我记得一排龙舌兰
That you... uh, I remember shots of tequila lined up.
我记得 说错了你纠正 橙绿色内衣
I remember, correct me if I'm wrong, lime green underwear.
更多的是薄荷绿
More of a minty green.
哦 我明白了
Oh, I see.
但是我确实记得你把我喝趴下了
I do remember you drinking me under the table, though..
这是干嘛 早晨例会?
What's this, an early briefing?
约翰 你来了 好极了
John, there you are, good.
这位是马库斯・杰克斯
This is Marcus Jakes,
- 是个卧底 - 没错
- he's a U.C. - Right.
嘿 约翰・莫兰德 终于见到真人了
Hey. John Moreland, in the flesh.
- 哥们 听过你很多事情 - 你好
- The stories I hear about you, brother. - How you doing?
杰克斯和我一起加入警队 一个警局
Jakes and I were in uniform together. Same division.
世界真小啊
Small world.
我过去经常逗她开心
I used to make her laugh so hard
弄得她连咖啡都呛到鼻子里
that coffee would shoot out her nose.
她现在还这样吗?
She still do that?
- 一直都这样 - 好吧 所以 简报
- All the time. - Okay. So. Briefing.
- 是啊 - 是的
- Right. - Yeah.
阿里・雷曼 专门收保护费
Ali Raman, runs a protection racket.
非法赌博 严刑 谋杀
Illegal gambling, torture, murder.
他有个地下搏击场 生意相当火爆
He's got an underground fight club, it's pretty intense.
是的 我听说过这家伙 他就是个疯子
Yeah, I've heard of this guy, he's a borderline psychopath.
杰克斯打入内部卧底
Jakes has been deep undercover.
- 八个月 - 厉害啊
- Eight months. - Cool.
我已经在他的组织做到了副手
My path into Raman's operation has been through his lieutenant.
一个叫瑞克・加齐的
A guy named Ric Gazi.
- 哦 看啊 - 是魔术
- Oh. Look at that. - It's magic.
好吧 我卧底在加齐的组织
Ok, I'm in deep with Gazi...
一路从他的手下做起
Worked my way onto his crew.
你一直在做什么?
And you've been doing what?
你知道的 收收钱
You know, collections.
砸砸店铺 吓吓人什么的
Trashing stores, intimidating folks, that kind of thing.
我现在就能逮捕加齐
I could arrest Gazi right now,
但是他不是我的重点
but he is not my focus.
我想要的是这个人
I want this guy.
我想抓雷曼 幕后老大
I want Raman, I want the boss.
重案组要求我们协助
Major Crimes is asking us to help out.
为什么 你的管理员呢?
Why, where's your handler?
他的管理员是是斯图・克劳德 他现在不在了
The handler was Stu Crowder, he's out of the picture.
不在了 这是什么意思?
Out of the picture, what does that suppose to mean?
他怎么了?
What happened to him?
哦 威士忌
Uh, whiskey...
先是威士忌 再是杜松子酒 如果有的话
...happened to him. Followed by gin, followed by paint thinner,
油漆稀释剂
if that's what he had around.
过了一阵子 他就不来找我了
After a while he just stopped checking in.
我要求全面监控还有支援
I'd called for surveillance, and backup,
结果什么都没有
I get nothing.
我全靠我自己
I was completely on my own.
杰克斯先生 我们能为你做什么?
So, what can we do for you, Mr. Jakes?
我的加齐宝贝 野心勃勃
My boy Gazi, he's got ambitions.
他打算做掉雷曼 计划找杀手来做
He's wants to take out Raman. He's planning a hit.
我们不能坐视不理
We can't let that happen.
- 所以我们要先下手为强 - 嗯
- So we're going to get in front of it. - Mh-hmm...
你会是我的老朋友 杀手约翰
You are going to be my old friend John the hit-man.
我会把你介绍给加齐
I'm going to introduce you to Gazi.
你会去见他 和他聊聊 和他达成协议
You're gonna meet him, you're gonna talk to him, you're gonna take the contract.
然后我就可以抓他了
And then we pick him up.
意图谋杀 罪名不小
Conspiracy to murder, that's big.
是的 我不想让他耽误我的案子
Yeah, I need him out of the way.
我要抓的是他的老板
I need a clear shot at his boss.
我想雷曼进监狱 不是要他死
I want Raman in prison, not dead.
好了 听着 我们第一步
Alright, listen up. Our first step...
稍等一下
Just wait a second.
你怎么知道这次暗杀是他策划的?
How do you know about this hit he's got planned?
他告诉我的
He told me.
所以你没有建议他这样做
So you didn't offer?
没有 当然没有
No, of course not.
你想说什么?
What's your point?
我想说 我想知道我到底
My point is, is just I want to know
走进的是个什么样的局
what I'm walking myself into here.
要确保这次会面没有问题
Make sure this meet is clean.
放松 我知道自己在做什么
Relax. I know what I'm doing.
这次行动没问题
The job is solid.
杰西 你从内部接应
Jesse, you'll cover things from the inside,
你去做拳手 在雷曼的俱乐部训练
you'll be a fighter, training at Raman's club.
你是我们在那的眼线
You'll be our eyes in there.
我需要给你装上监听装置
I'm going to have to wire you.
看你的衣服 我只能把东西安在你的前胸上了
With what you're wearing, I'm gonna have to do your chest.
- 能吧衣服脱了吗? - 好的
- Can you take your shirt off? - Yeah.
开什么玩笑?
Are you kidding me?
怎么了?
What?
没什么
Nothing.
过来
Come here.
加齐会在他的俱乐部 那是他在那做生意
Gazi will be at the club, that's where he does business.
杰克斯 你带约翰进去 把他介绍给加齐
Jakes, you're gonna walk John inside, introduce him.
我们会录下所有的谈话内容
We'll be recording everything.
一旦加齐让约翰达成协议 我们就抓到他了
As soon as Gazi offers John the contract, we got him.
好的 他们刚进来
Alright, they just came in.
杰西 一定要盯住他们
Jesse, make sure you keep them in sight.
收到
Copy that.
表面看来一切都合法
On the face of it is completely legit,
但是几个小时之后一切就完全变样了
but after hours it's a whole different thing.
不戴手套 赤拳搏击 赌注很大 代价惨重
The gloves come off, bare knuckle fights. A lot of gambling, a lot of blood.
就没有被关停过吗?
They never get shut down?
没有 从来没有
No, never.
雷曼知道买通谁 花多少钱
Raman knows exactly who to pay off, and exactly how much.
那边的那个家伙
The guy in there right now,
我后面的家伙 绿T恤
the guy behind me, green shirt,
是教练达菲  伊莱・达菲
that's the trainer Duffy, Eli Duff.
拳手都是由他负责
He runs all the fighters.
每个拳手还是俱乐部的保镖
Every single one of them does double duty as enforcers.
和他在一起的那个孩子 是加文
The kid in there with him, that's Gavin.
如果你不还钱 他就会来 打断你的胳膊
If you don't pay your debt, he comes by, he breaks your arms.
好的
Ok.
那边的那位 就是加齐
So, over there. That's my guy Gazi,
雷曼的副手
Raman's second in command.
他想除掉雷曼这样可以接管整个组织
He wants Raman gone so he can take over the whole operation.
他疑心很重 所以别介意
He's a little paranoid, so don't take it personally.
他在计划除掉老板
Well, he's planning to kill his boss,
我要是他我也会疑心重重的
I'd be paranoid too.
他们在接近加齐
They're approaching Gazi.
他来了
There he is.
怎么 喔 等等 等等 等一下
What... whoa, wait, wait, wait for it, wait.
那家伙说对不起 以后不会晚了
Chewy says he's sorry, won't be late again.
别说我没给你钱
Don't say I never gave you nothing.
哦 这位是我朋友 就是那个人
Oh, this is my friend. This is the guy.
我跟你说过的那个
The guy I told you about.
你好 我是约翰
How you doing? John.
他很有两下子 参过军
He does the thing, the service.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我怎么跟你说的?他不喜欢新面孔就是他
What did I tell you? He hates new people, this guy.
加齐 我么谈过的 你需要一个人
Gazi, we had the conversation, you wanted to meet a guy,
你眼前的就是
now you're meeting him.
什么情况?
What's happening?
我不知道 好像被耍了
I don't know. Looks like a stand off.
朋友 你想多了吧
You're imagining things, my friend.
马上走人吧
You need to walk away right now.
我告诉过他这不是个好主意
I told him this was a bad idea.
这家伙 根本听不懂话
He's got zero judgment, this guy.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你觉得他会在众目睽睽之下说这事 得了吧
You think he's going to discuss business in front of all these people? Come on.
抱歉 快点 我们走吧
Apologize. Come on, let's go.
你玩死我了 你知道吗?
You're killing me here, you know that?
告诉他我们换个地方再见 砖厂 北面
Tell him we're gonna meet somewhere else. Brickworks, north side.
- 好的 - 停车场那儿
- Yes. - In the parking lot.
好的 好办法
Alright that'll work, that's good.
我会去问他的
I'll ask him.
砖厂 北面 停车场
Brickworks, north side, parking lot.
二十分钟后见 最后机会
Be there in twenty minutes, your last chance.
好的 他们要出来了
Alright, they're on their way out.
我们在车里等 让加齐来找我们
We're going to wait here in the car. Let Gazi come to us.
等他坐进来了 让他主导谈话
When he comes in, let him drive the conversation.
- 别引导他 好吗? - 好的
- Don't lead him, alright? - All right.
玛利亚和丹尼会在两点钟方向待命
Maria and Danny are going to be at 2 o'clock running spin.
他们怎么想的弄个车窗贴膜的车
What's he thinking with these tinted windows,
加齐坐到后排我们怎么能看得见
how are we going to see Gazi when he's in the backseat?
丽贝卡停在我们后面她会看着入口的
Rebecca will be in the lot behind us. She'll have eyes on the entrance.
丽贝卡来了
Here's Rebecca.
好了 她就位了
Ok, she's in position.
看到丽贝卡真好 她看起来好极了
It's good to see Rebecca, she looks good.
你们合作还好吗?
You two getting along?
大多数时间还行
Most of the time.
是的 她是需要时间适应一下
Yeah, she takes a while that one.
你们会好起来的
You two will be fine.
她绝对值得合作
She's worth it.
她是最好的 真的
She's one of a kind, seriously.
我认识的最好的警察
The best cop I've ever known.
约翰 加齐进入大门
John, Gazi's approaching the entrance.
准备
Get ready.
我们看见了
We got eyes.
好的 他来了
OK, here he is.
不错 加齐是一个人来的
We're good, Gazi's alone.
约翰 你能看清楚吗?
John, do you have a clear view?
是的 没问题
Yeah, we're good.
- 他干嘛呢? - 他是要出来吗?
- What is he doing? - Is he gonna get out?
放心 他只是比较小心而已
Relax. He's just being cautious.
快点啊 加齐
Come on, Gazi.
好了 我们开始了
Alright, here we go.
丽贝卡 有人开枪
Shots fired, Rebecca
枪手在哪?
Where's... where's the shooter?
在那 货仓那边
There he is, by the warehouse.
丹尼尔 盯住他
Daniel, stay with him.
我看见他了 看见了
I got him. I got him,
朝南逃去 我们正在追捕
he's headed south. We're in pursuit.
有枪击发生 砖厂北面停车场
Shots fired. Brickworks, north side parking lot,
马上派救护车
send an ambulance.
好了 坚持住
Alright, hold on.
我想说的是这一切都仅仅依靠杰克斯的消息
All I'm saying is this whole thing is based on Jakes' information.
杰克斯的判断 对吧?
Jakes' judgment, all right?
如果他干得好 他应该知道暗杀的事
If he was doing his job, he would have known about the hit.
但是你不是在指责他
But you're not placing blame.
不 我没有在指责他
No I'm not placing blame.
丽贝卡 等一下好吗?
Rebecca, wait, okay?
我以前和这样的人合作过好吗?
I've worked with guys like this before, all right?
- 他们独断专行 - 你不是?
- They fly by the seat of their pants. - And you don't?
如果加齐被做掉 他就会做到
If Gazi was exposed... he should have been on top of that...
他不知道会这样 约翰
He didn't know it was going to happen, John.
要是你 你也会做这样的决定
You would have made the same call.
我知道这家伙是你朋友 好吗
I know this guy's a friend of yours, all right,
但是也许你对他有盲区 这点你想过吗?
but maybe you've got a blind spot for this guy. Do you ever think of that?
他是个好警察 你说话小心点
He's a good cop, you need to back off.
瑞克・加齐在西奈医院死亡
Ric Gazi was DOA at Mount Sinai.
凶杀组要你打电话
Homicide wants you to call.
这还用说
I'm sure they do.
你需要作出全面报告 我们都需要
You're gonna have to give a full statement. We all are.
- 凶手呢? - 跑了
- Shooter? - He got away.
伙计们 我不知道 我发誓
I had no idea guys, I swear to God.
那么到底怎么回事 雷曼收到风声了?
So, what happened. Raman caught wind of the hit?
知道他的手下要杀他 就先下手了?
Found out his boy's coming after him, got there first?
是的 一定是这样的
Yeah, must have been.
也许是先发制人
Could have been a pre-emptive strike.
杰克斯 意味着你也完了
It means you might be done, Jakes.
太糟糕了 八个月的努力就这么泡汤了
Too bad. That's eight months work down the drain.
或者这对我有利
Or maybe it works in my favor.
这是个机会 往上走的好机会
It's an opportunity, maybe it's a chance to move up.
怎么说?
How do you figure that?
你是加齐的人 怎么能逃的过雷曼的眼睛
You're one of Gazi's boys, Raman's going to smell you a mile away.
伙计们 我现在需要做的事就是行动
All I gotta do is make a move, guys.
我传出消息 向雷曼表示衷心
I just gotta send a message.
让他知道我没参与这事
Show Raman that I'm loyal, that I wasn't involved.
约翰说的对 你可能就是下一个目标
John could be right. You could be next in line for a bullet.
如果我的人和你一起 我的人也有危险
And if my guys are with you, they're in danger too.
我们需要确保杰克斯的安全
We need to make sure Jakes is safe.
这是我们下一步要做的
That's our next move.
我们可以安插杰西进去
We could put Jesse in
充当拳手和保镖 也许?
as a fighter slash enforcer, maybe?
他已经加入俱乐部了 有掩护的身份了
He's already been in the club. He's established.
约翰?
John?
是的 他也许想挣点钱
Yeah, he could be looking for extra cash.
杰克斯 你可以带他进去 介绍一下
Jakes, you can walk him in, make the intro.
他可以充当你的手下
He could be one of your boys.
这样看起来行得通
It'll give us a sense.
如果有人打你的主意 杰克斯
If anyone looks at you sideways, Jakes,
任务结束 我们立刻撤出
that's it, we're out.
收到
Copy that.
小子 我希望你知道怎么打拳
Kid, I hope you know how to fight.
天才少年 速成选手
Raw talent, quick learner.
你需要人帮你收钱 他也可以
You need a guy to do collections, he can do that too.
你说你在找新人
You said you were looking for new people.
你好?
How you doing?
你在哪认识他的?
Where'd you find him?
我认识的以女孩儿 他是她弟弟
This girl I know, he's her kid brother.
她都快疯了 她觉得他是下一个巨星
She's insane, she thinks he's the next big thing.
也许她是对的
Maybe she's right.
是的 听着 小子 这个是达菲
Yeah, listen kid, this is Duffy,
他让你做什么你就做什么 明白了吗?
you do exactly what he says, all right?
是的
Yeah.
让他和加文试试 看他怎么样
Throw him in there with Gavin, see what he does.
我的手下不和新来的打
First spar doesn't go to one of my boys.
新来的和我打
It goes to me.
祝你好运
Good luck, kid.
好了 我们开始吧
Alright, here we go.
达菲 悠着点
Take it easy on him, Duff.
加油 杰西 好了 别浪费机会
Come on, Jesse, here we go, make this count.
顶住 跟上 跟上
Keep it together. Let's go, let's go.
注意他的脚步 加油
Watch his feet, c'mon.
就这样 就这样 等待机会
That's it, that's it, wait for an opening.
没事 你行的 加油
That's alright, you got this, c'mon!
没事
Shake it off.
加油 跟上他 行的行的
Come on, stay on him. Let's go, let's go.
好了 达菲 我想差不多了
Alright, Duffy, I think you made your point.
好了 我想你可以让他起来了
Alright, you can let him up I think.
他都喘不了气了
He can't breathe.
哥们 让他起来吧 你在干什么?
Let him up, man. What are you doing?
这小子没事 让他过后来找我
Your boy's okay. Tell him to come see me later.
顺便说一句 你战术对了
You made the right choice, by the way.
他有个前交叉步 你看到了只是没抓到机会
You had a front cross. You saw it, but you didn't take it.
你让达菲骗了
You let Duffy smoke you.
你看到了?
You noticed?
我第一次也这样
I did the same thing, my first time.
你在这没问题
You're gonna do just fine here.
走吧
Come on.
我不是告诉你了吗?我很安全 我们没事
What'd I tell you? I'm safe, we're good to go.
你有什么消息了?
What have you got?
好的 稍安勿躁
All right. Bear with me.
雷曼除了收保护费还要其他的生意对吧?
Raman is in the business, among other things, of collecting debts, right?
有时他从别人那买来债权
And sometimes he buys a debt from someone else.
比如 你是个赌徒 你是赌徒丹
For example, you're a gambler. You're Gambler Dan.
你欠约翰二十五万 三十万 你没还上
And you owe John here, two-fifty, three hundred grand. You're not paying.
约翰是我的一老朋友
And Gentleman John here is an old friend of mine
很早就认识 你知道的 他不是十分暴力
from way back, you know, he's not a violent man.
他不能到处打断别人的手指
He can't go around breaking people's fingers,
实在是没那胆量
he doesn't have the stomach for it.
所以把债权转给雷曼 他也许花五万买下
So I bring Raman the debt, and he buys it for, say, I don't know, 50 grand.
他就是个收账公司
He's like a collection agent.
现在赌徒丹就是欠他钱了
Now Gambler Dan owes him.
如果他不付钱 他的腿就废了
And if he doesn't pay, his legs get broken.
但是我们已经有身份了 约翰是个杀手
But we've already established, John as a hit-man.
但是没人知道啊
But no one knows that.
他们只是看见他进俱乐部了
They only saw him in the club.
那他为什么进去呢?
So why was he in the club?
- 你当时把他介绍给加齐 - 没错
- You were introducing him to Gazi. - Right.
是因为加齐要买下的债权
Because of the debt Gazi was going to buy.
但是现在加齐死了
And now that Gazi's dead...
你就需要找雷曼谈谈
You're going to take it all the way up to Raman.
是的 这就是我一直在说的行动
Yes... This is the move I've been waiting to make.
雷曼去找赌徒丹
Raman goes after gambler Dan...
就在他要打断丹的手指时
And just as he's about to break some fingers...
我们的梦幻小组出现 全副武装 实施抓捕
In comes the dream team. Guns a'blazin. Ready to make some arrests.
放高利贷 敲诈勒索 袭击他人
Loan sharking, extortion, assault.
伙计们 你们怎么想?
Guys, what do you think?
不错啊
It's not terrible.
有什么意见?
Thoughts?
我们行动吧 看看效果
Let's do it. Let's take it for a spin.
谁啊?
Yes?
马库斯
Marcus.
这位是约翰・贝恩
This is John Bain.
很荣幸 请坐
Pleasure. Please sit.
马库斯告诉我你的小状况
Marcus, has told me about your predicament.
我爱我的妹妹
I love my sister.
只是她选男人的眼光实在是不怎么样
Only she has terrible taste in men.
他是个赌徒 他们一起两年了
He's a gambler, they were together for two years.
他从她那儿偷了三十万
He stole three hundred thousand from her.
当她发现的时候 他就对她拳脚相加
And when she found out, he became very violent.
他差一点要了她的命
He almost killed her.
你现在想把自己的钱要回来
And now you want your money back.
我想要他付出代价
I want him to pay.
我希望你能亲自处理这事 我听说你是最好的
I want your personal attention on this. I hear you're the best.
可以吗?
Can you do it?
也许
Possibly.
我需要时间让加文查一下他
I'll need time to have Gavin check him out.
你随意
Whatever you need.
他住在西艾尔姆大街十九号
He lives at 19 West Elm Street.
约翰有个特别的请求
John has a special request.
说
Go ahead.
当你做的时候我要在场
I want to be there when you do it.
你收钱的时候
When you collect.
当你收拾他的时候 我想看着他的眼睛
I want to look into his eyes, when you're making him pay.
嘿 约翰让我查一下杰克斯的档案
Hey. John asked me to check into Jakes' files.
真的?
Really?
是的 而且我觉得我们可能有麻烦了
Yeah, and I think we might have a problem.
我把杰克斯过去八个月的
So I've been pulling all of Jakes' case work
案子都调了出来 各种问题
from the last eight months. And it's full of holes.
我一点都不吃惊 他的管理员消失了
I'm not surprised, the handler was AWOL...
是的 我不确定是管理员的问题
Yeah, I'm not so sure it's just the handler.
我是说 他有很多的书面东西 但是没有证据
I mean, he's got paper, just not a lot of evidence.
没有视频 没有音频
There's no video, there's no audio.
他手写的报告也十分简略
His hand-written notes are sketchy at best.
这里没有能在法庭上站得住脚的东西
There's nothing here that would stand up in court.
还有一个女人 艾比・兰德
And there's this woman, Abi Rand.
杰克斯拿她当线人
Jakes has been using her as a CI.
曾是海洛因成瘾者
Former heroin addict.
她的线索没有导致任何抓捕
Her information hasn't led to a single arrest,
但是他还一直给她钱
and yet he keeps paying her.
好几千块白花了
Thousands of dollars for nothing.
听着 这一切一定能解释的通的
Look, this all could have an explanation,
但是如果杰克斯对我们撒谎
but if Jakes is lying to us,
如果他已经失控了
if he's out of control...
你是说他和自己的线人上床
So he's sleeping with his C.I.
可能是的
Probably, yeah.
我去把她带过来 和她谈谈
I'm going to bring her in, talk to her.
- 你看卷宗了吗? - 一团乱麻
- Have you looked at the case work? - It's a mess.
也许是管理员
It could be the handler.
你把这些推到管理员头上?
You're going to blame the handler on this one?
我了解杰克斯 他不会像这样搞砸一个案子的
I know Jakes, he would never jeopardize a case like this.
丽贝卡那是十五年前的事了
Rebecca, you knew him fifteen years ago.
如果你问我 我觉得你应该现在就取消行动
If you ask me, I think you should shut down this whole thing right now.
也许他卧底太久
Maybe he's been in too long...
丽贝卡
Rebecca?
约翰 他相信我
He believed in me, John.
他曾是第一个
He was the first.
他过去总说
He use to say,
你去哪 我去哪
"I'd follow you anywhere."
不论有多危险
"I'd walk off a cliff for you."
这件事上有证据前我相信他是无罪的
I'm giving him the benefit of the doubt on this.
- 那个线人叫什么名字? - 艾比
- What's the C.I.'s name? - Abi.
好吧 等她来了 让玛利亚和她谈
Alright, when she comes in, Maria should talk to her,
你不行
not you.
我们得确定我们可以相信杰克斯
We need to know we can trust Jakes.
在那之前 案子由我自己负责 行吗
Until then, I'll look after things myself, all right?
我会在临时房子那帮杰西
I'll cover Jesse at the set-up house.
丹尼尔那边演完了 我们就行动
Soon as Daniel checks out Raman, we move.
按照杰克斯的安排做 赌徒丹
Put Jakes' play in action, Gambler Dan.
你要进去 到里面看一下吗?
You want to head over, take a look inside?
暂时不用 我们老实坐在这
Not yet. We're gonna sit tight.
看看都什么人进出这里
See who comes and goes.
如果他不给钱怎么办?
So what happens if he won't pay?
收拾一下?
Rough him up a little?
我们就是做监视的 就这些
We're just doing research, that's all.
好了 他们就位了
Alright, they're in place.
我们等几分钟
Let's give it a few minutes.
我好了 等你指令了
I'm ready. Just say the word.
我这儿努力想搞清楚状况
I'm just trying to figure this whole thing out.
老板是雷曼
So, the boss is Raman.
和加齐 他被开枪击中 死了
And Gazi, he got shot, he's dead.
但是之后是达菲 他变成了下命令的 对吧?
But then, Duffy, he's the one who gives you the orders, right?
你问题问的有点多
You ask a lot of questions.
无所谓了 我们也不是非得聊天
Whatever, we don't have to talk.
好了 丹尼尔 随时开始
Okay, Daniel. Any time.
他来了
Here he is.
车不错啊
Sweet car.
至少十万啊 没错吧
That's a hundred grand easy, right there.
是的 就是他 是我们要找的人 毫无疑问呢
Yeah, that's him, that's our guy. No question
- 开什么玩笑? - 怎么?
- Are you kidding me? - What?
稍等一下
Hang on a sec.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
我不敢相信
I don't believe it.
- 就是他逮捕的我 - 什么?
- That guy arrested me. - What?
七八年前吧 这家伙是警察
Like seven, eight years ago. That guy's a cop!
什么?你确定?
What? You're sure?
哥们那是我第一次被抓
My first bust, man.
我永远都忘不了那张脸
I'll never forget his face.
丹尼尔 你被认出来了
Daniel, you just got made.
你开什么玩笑
You're kidding me.
你暴露了 待在房子里面 别让人看见
You're busted. Stay in the house, stay out of sight.
天啊 这机会有多大?
Man, what are the friggin' odds?
那么我们怎么办?
So what are we gonna do?
你觉得我们能怎么办? 我们得告诉老板
What do you think we're gonna do? We're going to tell the boss.
真他妈的
Son of a...
啊 不是吧
Ah, come on...
你在干吗呢?
What are you doing?
你打算告诉我我这是在哪吗?
You want to tell me where I am?
艾比 我是侦探警员科尔特兹
Abi, I'm Detective Constable Cortez.
我被捕了?
Am I under arrest?
你是马库斯・杰克斯的线人吗?
Are you a confidential informant for Marcus Jakes?
这是你的线人编号吗?
Is this your C.I. number?
这东西我应该记下来吗?
Was I supposed to memorize it?
那这个呢 是你的签名吗?
What about this, is that your signature?
嗯
Mm-Hmm.
马库斯在哪?
Where's Marcus?
有很多钱是付给你的
These are all payments made to you,
换取信息的 现在看来都是假消息
in exchange for information. False information by the looks of it.
但是他一直给你钱
But he kept paying you.
艾比 你和他上床了吗?
Are you sleeping with him, Abi?
他不是花钱买我
He's not paying me for sex.
马库斯・杰克斯是你男朋友?
Is Marcus Jakes your boyfriend?
如果他是会怎样?
So what if he is?
我懂了 艾比 你可能以为
I get it, Abi. You probably thought
这事不会给你带来麻烦的
you'd never get in trouble for this.
我是说他可是个警察啊 对吧?
I mean he's a cop, right?
但 事实是 情报是假的
Here's the thing, though, it's bogus information.
法庭上是不承认的 你们俩都知道
It won't hold up in court. You both knew it.
是违法的
That's an offence.
我现在就应该拘捕你
I should arrest you, right now.
- 我想和马库斯谈一下 - 不可能
- I want to talk to Marcus. - That's not happening.
我不能进监狱 好吗?
I can't go to jail, okay?
我不能 我不可以的
I can't. I can't do that.
我给你看点东西
I need to show you something.
知道这个人是谁吗?
Do you know who this man is?
艾比?
Abi?
能告诉我他的名字吗
Can you tell me his name.
是奇普
That's Chip.
- 我前男友 - 你知道谁干的吗?
- That's my ex. - Do you know who did this to him?
他跟踪我 老来烦我
He was stalking me, he wouldn't leave me alone.
艾比 他差点没命了
Abi. He almost died.
谁干的? 是谁?
Who did this? Who was it?
是马库斯 马库斯干的
It was Marcus. Marcus did it.
奇普来我家 马库斯发疯了
Chip came by my apartment and Marcus just lost it.
我以为他要杀了他
I thought he was gonna kill him.
哥们 你怎么来了 来干吗?
What are you doing man, what are you doing here?
- 嘿 我能进来吗? - 是的 请进
- Hey, can I come in? - Yeah, come on in.
哦 等你一会儿
Uh... Give me a minute.
- 好的 - 好的
- Alright. - Yeah.
地方不错
Nice digs.
是的 不会引人怀疑 是吧?
Yeah, it does the job, right?
这地方有监控吗?
This place wired?
卧室的坏了 但是你知道的
Bedroom's on the fritz, but you know...
是的
Yeah.
- 给你 - 谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
昨天熬得挺晚啊?
So you had a late night last night?
你来这干吗 怎么了?
What are we doing here, what's going on?
丽贝卡担心这个案子
Rebecca's worried about the case.
她想让你去趟总部
She wants you to come in.
还有什么新情况? 她爱操心 女人啊
What else is new? She loves to worry, that girl.
你来就是为了告诉我这个? 打个电话就行了
That what you came by, to tell me? Could've just called.
- 你电话打不通 - 语音留言啊
- Your phone's off. - I would've got the message.
丹尼那边怎么样?
So how's Danny-boy?
我们设的局进行的如何?
How's our play shaking out?
丹尼尔
Daniel...
被认出来了
got made.
- 他 什么? - 是的
- He, what? - Yup.
- 他做什么了? - 加文  那个打手
- What did he do? - The muscle guy, Gavin.
很久以前丹尼尔抓过他
Turns out Daniel arrested him back in the day.
- 你开玩笑吧 - 不是
- You're kidding me. - Nope.
运气不好 没办法
That's just bad luck, that's what that is.
这案子好像一直这样
Seems to happen a lot on this case.
问你点事
Let me ask you something.
如果我检查整个地方
If I were to go through this whole place,
我会发现哪些非法的东西?
what kind of contraband would I find?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
杰克斯 我也做过卧底
Jakes, I've been here.
这事我也干过
I've done all this.
好吗 我知道诱惑
Okay? I know the temptations.
我想骗你 我得相当的厉害
I must be good if I'm fooling you.
哥们 你被外表骗了 都是道具
You're falling for the look, man. The props.
我很清白
I'm squeaky clean.
知道吗 约翰?
You know what, John?
我原以为在所有人中你是最了解我的
I would have thought you of all people would know what I'm doing here.
除了我是谁之外其他的都得忘记
I had to forget everything, but who I was.
就当这个人
Just to be this guy.
我每天看见有人被打 而我就站在那
I watch guys get beaten every day and I just gotta stand there.
你觉得我喜欢?
You think that's fun for me?
我在尽一个警察的职责 你帮还是不帮我?
I'm doing police work, are you going to help me or what?
我们和艾比谈过了 我们请她过去的
We talked to Abi. We brought her in.
她什么都说了
She told us the full extent.
她准备作证了
She's prepared to testify.
- 全说什么了?  - 你一直在收账
- The full extent of what? - You've been collecting debts.
那些人被打的时候你就在场
You've been there when guys have gotten beaten.
你不仅仅是在那看 而且你也参与其中了
And you haven't just been watching, you've been doing it yourself.
不不不 只是为了掩护 不是真的 她不明白
No no no, that's the cover, it's not real, she doesn't understand
- 伙计们 - 你一直在给你线人钱
- Guys... - You've funneling cash to your C.I.
你在挣钱但是却不上报
You've been making money and not reporting it.
不是真的 - 你了解我的
That's not true. - You know me,
你知道我是什么样的人
you know what I'm like.
如果是真的 我会查出来的
If it's true, I'm gonna find out.
我跟这个案子已经八个月了
I've been working this case for eight months.
这是我的梦想啊 我怎么会毁了这个案子呢?
I dream of this, why would I put that in jeopardy?
你喜欢上这种生活 你喜欢现在的角色
You like the lifestyle you like playing the part.
你离不开了
You don't want to leave it.
丽贝卡 你就是这么想的?
Is that what you think, Rebecca?
这家伙就是这么告诉你的?
Is that what this guy's telling you?
我对天起誓 马库斯 我不知道该怎么想
I swear to God, Marcus, I don't know what to think.
好吧 这个约翰什么 我也听说过他的好多事
Okay, this guy John-boy, I've heard a lot of stories.
你不会认为他有时也违反点规定?
You don't think he bent the rules sometimes?
好吧 听着 这家伙是个施虐狂
Okay look, this guy was abusive.
他老是来骚扰她 我担心她
He wouldn't leave her alone, I was worried for her.
案子没问题
The case is good.
这么说他们知道丹尼尔是个警察? 这也可行
So what they know Daniel's a cop? That's workable.
我们可以利用一下 他不是第一个欠债的警察
We could use that, he's not the first cop to owe a debt.
他们不会知道他是我们的人
They'll never guess that's our cover.
丽贝卡 看着我
Rebecca, look at me.
得了吧 你知道我的 你知道我不会这样做的
Come on, you know me, you know I wouldn't do this.
我了解曾经的你
I know who you were.
我需要
I need it.
我需要抓住这个雷曼 他是个人渣
I need this Raman guy, he is a scumbag.
他践踏人们的生活
And he ruins people's lives.
经历这一切之后 我需要一个好结果
I need something good to come out of all this.
别把我变成一个
Don't turn me into the guy...
一个没管好自己 搞砸了大案子的警察
The cop who goes off the rails, and blows the big case.
别这样对我
Don't do it to me.
能让我们谈一下吗?
Can you give us a minute?
好的 好的
Yeah, yeah.
这个雷曼 手段残忍 他靠打人为生
This guy Raman, he's vicious, he beats people up for a living.
他就在我眼前杀了一个人
He killed someone right in front of us.
丽贝卡 我们得抓他
We need to get him, Rebecca.
听着 杰克斯走在边缘
Look, Jakes is on the edge,
他必须如此 这样才能接近雷曼
he has to be, it's what got him close to Raman.
我觉得杰克斯能行
I think Jakes can do it.
是吗? 经过这一切之后?
Really? After all this?
你要拿命来赌吗?
You're going to put your life in his hands?
你和我都清楚 现在站在门外的可能是我
You know as well as I do, that could be me outside that door right now..
你相信这个人
You believed in this guy.
我们给他个机会将功补过
Let's give him a chance to redeem himself.
我们扳倒雷曼
Let's take Raman down.
好消息是 加文不记得你的名字 只是你的脸
So the good news is, Gavin doesn't remember your name, just your face.
跟丹尼尔・温拿考特打个招呼
Say hello to Daniel Winacott.
你是反黑组的 就和真的丹尼尔一样
You're part of Guns and Gangs, just like the real Daniel.
两年前 你状况不断 违反纪律 表现不佳
And after a couple years, you blew it. Infractions, bad performance reports,
在赌桌上被抓 之后被降职做文员
caught in a few gambling dens and then down-graded to a desk job.
- 这么说我就是文职警员 - 脾气很大
- So, I'm a file-clerk. - With a temper.
还有赌博的嗜好 凡有重要比赛一定下注
And a gambling problem, you just can't resist a big fight.
听着 你觉得这能行?
Listen, you think this is going to work?
雷曼一直和警察打交道
Raman deals with cops all the time,
也许其中还有他最重要的客户
probably some of his best clients.
好了  今晚是雷曼俱乐部的拳击之夜
OK, It's fight night at Raman's club.
丹尼尔 你今晚去下注
Daniel, you're there to bet on the fight,
玛利亚你是她的新女友
and Maria, you're his new girlfriend.
杰克斯和约翰 你们联系雷曼
Jakes and John, you're gonna make contact with Raman,
把赌徒丹送给他
and deliver Gambler Dan right to him.
雷曼要做的就是试图收账
All Raman has to do is try and collect
我们就抓到他了 当场逮捕
and we got him, we'll take him down.
嘿 注意了 我要你看这
Yo, focus man, I need you here.
那小子表现怎么样?
How's our boy doing?
说实话 有点不靠谱
To be honest, a bit shaky.
但是他一定要拿下雷曼 他会撑下去的
But he's obsessed with Raman. He'll get through it.
- 是丽贝卡吗? 她担心我? - 她没事
- That Rebecca? She worried about me? - She's fine.
你这水平不行啊  得了吧 说吧
Is that the best you can do?  Come on, tell me.
杰克斯 我们身上有监听
Jakes, we're wired.
我才不管什么监听呢
I don't care about the wire.
跟我直说 约翰 这是我最后一天吗?
Give it to me straight, brother John. Is this my last day on the job?
这是我们搞定这个案子的最后一次机会
This is our last chance at this case.
我的意思是作为警察
I mean as a cop.
她要拿走我的警徽 是吗?
She's gonna take my badge, isn't she?
这由你来决定 听着 我们明天再谈
That's up to you. Look, we'll talk about that tomorrow.
今晚 我们把注意力放到抓坏人上 好吗?
Tonight, let's just focus on getting the bad guys, all right?
丽贝卡如果不是相信你 今晚是不会让你来的
Rebecca wouldn't put you in play if she didn't think you could do this.
你并不像我那么了解贝卡
You don't know Becks like I do.
一旦失去她的信任 就完了 是吧 丽贝卡?
Once you lose her trust, it's over. Right, Rebecca?
那么我们就重新赢得她的信任
Well you're going to have to earn it back.
杰克斯 你是个好警察
Jakes, you are good at this job.
你需要的就是不断提醒她 对吧?
You just got to remind her that, alright?
好吗? 好吗?
Okay? Okay?
好的 好的 好的
Yeah, yeah, okay.
注意了 目标出现
Heads up. Here comes the target.
想象一下我当时多么惊讶 当我发现
Imagine my surprise when I discovered that the man
你让我收账的那个人居然是个警察
you asked me to collect from is a cop.
他是 我本应告诉你的 但不想被拒绝
He is, I should have mentioned that to you. I didn't want you to say no.
马库斯 这事你知道吗? 你知道吗?
Did you know about this, Marcus? Did you know?
是我的错 我根本没告诉他
It's my fault I didn't even tell him.
听着 这个警察就是渣滓 他没有朋友
Look, this cop a screw-up. He has no friends.
没人会帮他报仇的 这点我保证
There will be no payback. You have my guarantee.
他现在就在吧台那边
He's over there at the bar right now.
带着他的新女友
He's with his new girlfriend.
你把他带到这了
You brought him here.
我带他来看拳赛向他示好
I brought him to the fight as a peace offering.
相信我 他完全不知道你要向他收账
Trust me, he has absolutely no idea you're about to collect on his debt.
听着 朋友 你今晚要赚大钱
Look, you're going to make a lot of money tonight, my friend.
到时候你再谢谢我吧
And you're going to have me to thank for that.
我们现在就开始吧 我叫他过来
Let's do it right now, I'll call him over.
不 让他在那待一会儿 没事的
No, leave him there for a minute, he's fine.
他玩的挺好的 我的问题是
He's enjoying himself. My problem is this.
我不喜欢警察
I don't like police.
而且和你实话实说
And to be perfectly honest,
我开始对你有点不放心了 杰克斯
I'm starting to have an uneasy feeling about you, Jakes.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
而我一直跟着感觉走的
And I always listen to that feeling.
他在做什么?
What's he doing?
打住 你为什么不做这一票呢?
Stop, why are you killing this?
不可能了 杰克斯 对不起
This is not happening. I'm sorry, Jakes.
今晚不行 好好看比赛吧
Not tonight. Enjoy the fight.
你还有你朋友
You and your friend.
就这样了? 他可以就这么走了
That's it? He can't just walk away.
他可以而且就这么走了
He can and he just did.
丽贝卡 我想我们只能这样了
Rebecca, I think we're done here.
你想再给他点时间 再回来?
You want to give him some time, circle back?
不 没用了 完了 没机会了
No, there's no point. It's over. He just closed the door.
不是吧 开设么玩笑? 你们就这么放弃了?
Come on, are you kidding me? You're just giving up?
淡定 杰克斯 我们没戏了
Calm down Jakes, we're done.
那又怎样? 我们就这样放弃?
So what? We're just shutting down?
我们收拾一下吧
Let's pack it up.
伙计们 开始了
Here we go, boys.
不能打头 打眼睛 腹股沟
No head butts, eye gouging, groin attacks,
或者用脚踢头部来压制对手
or head kicking to a grounded opponent.
- 好吧 我们开始吧 - 下一次 好吗?
- Alright, so that's it I guess. - Next time, right?
我们回去见
I'll see you back at the shop.
好的 但是我今晚在这看比赛
Okay, but I'm staying for the fight.
要干吗啊 想看拳赛?
What do you wanna do, wanna watch the fight?
这事没完
It's not over.
杰克斯
Jakes!
你以为你就可以这么大摇大摆走了?
You think you can just walk away?
你以为我们就这么完了?
You think we're done?
回来
Come here!
你去哪?
Where do you go?
杰克斯
Jakes.
你要干吗?
What are you doing?
他没带枪
He's unarmed.
他必须告诉我们一切
He's going to tell us everything.
每一起罪行 每一个细节
Every crime, every detail.
要不然我就一枪崩了他
Or I'm going to put a bullet in him.
嘿 约翰哪去了? 你看见他了吗?
Hey, where's John? Have you seen him?
没有 也没看见杰克斯
No, and no Jakes.
- 你觉得这样会好用? - 他会说的
- You think this is gonna work? - He's gonna confess.
他会说的 我么们打到他说为止
He's gonna say we beat it out of him.
然后我们不承认就行了
And then we're gonna deny it.
你说我们是什么意思?
What do you mean "we"?
我是说你和我 你会支持我的
I, mean you and me. You're gonna get my back.
- 你想让我替你说谎? -  是的
- You want me to lie for you? - Yes.
约翰 八个月 我追踪这个家伙已经八个月了
Eight months, John, I've been after this guy for eight months.
我不能就这么放他走
I'm not just gonna let him go.
如果你干不了 你就给我走
If you're not up for it, you leave.
醒醒
Wake up!
好了 杰克斯
Alright, Jakes.
别这样 别这么做
Come on, don't do this.
这次我会支持你的 好吗?
I'm gonna back you up on this one, okay?
我们说是他来追杀你的 是自卫
We'll say he came after you, it was self-defense.
你不会被起诉的
You will not be charged.
但是这之后 杰克斯 你不要再做下去了
But after that, Jakes, you've got to walk away from this one.
现在 你需要马上离开
Right now, you need to walk away.
醒醒
Wake up!
玛利亚 怎么了?
Maria, what's going on in there?
杰克斯和约翰哪去了?
Jakes and John, where are they?
我们留他们在那看拳赛了
We left them watching the fight.
- 那雷曼呢? - 他也不在
- What about Raman? - He's not here either.
找到他们
Find them.
我们分开行动
We gotta split up.
我也经历过这种情况好吗?
I've been where you are. All right?
多谢这份工作 我离婚了
Thanks to this job... I've racked up a divorce,
住在一个阴冷的公寓里 我都懒得打开行李
I got a bleak apartment I can barely unpack,
我晚上躺在床上睡不着
I lie awake in my bed at night
一肚子怨气 一肚子怒火
full of anger, full of this constant rage.
不错啊
Good for you.
哦 他醒了
Awww, there he is!
等一下 杰克斯 我懂 好吗?
Wait, Jakes, I get it, all right?
哦 不 你不懂
Oh no, you don't get it.
这家伙虐打好人 以此为乐
This guy tortures people, and takes pleasure from doing it!
他会交代的 对着电话 否则我就崩了他
And he's gonna say it, into the phone or I'm gonna put a bullet in his brain.
说啊 说啊 告诉我你怎么虐打别人的
Talk, tell it! Tell me how you torture people!
你说的对 这家伙是个人渣
You're right. This guy is scum.
- 说啊 - 他是个畜生 他活该
- Talk! - He's an animal, he deserves it.
好吧 你可以现在就杀了他
Okay, you could kill him right now,
没人会为他难过的
no one would shed a tear.
我得告诉你
Let me tell you something...
如果你这么做了 你杀了他
if you do that, if you shoot him,
你也会迷失的 朋友
you will be lost, my friend.
你就完了
You are done.
你永远不会恢复过来 永远
You will never come back from that, ever again.
你懂我的意思吗?
You understand me?
杰克斯
Jakes,
现在你就在边缘上徘徊
right now you are standing on the edge.
你需要退一步
You need to step back now.
就一步
Just one step back.
好吗 我就在这
Come on, I'm right here.
我不逼你
I'm not forcing you.
好吗
Come on.
你必须退一步
You gotta step back.
- 你会起诉他吗? - 我会尽力的
- You're gonna charge him? - I'm gonna try.
- 杰克斯 - 你得逮捕我
- Jakes. - You need to arrest me.
- 你得把我抓起来 - 对不起
- You need to take me in. - I'm sorry.
我们走吧
Let's go.
听起来很奇怪
This is gonna sound strange.
我很高兴是你
I'm glad it was you.
丹尼尔
Daniel.
想过来帮我打开行李吗?
Want to come and help me unpack?
这有两瓶啤酒
There's a couple beer in it for you.
挺有吸引力的 但是我今晚有事
Tempting, but I got a thing tonight.
伙计 那就是你的损失了
Well, that's your loss, pal.
好吧 给我留瓶冰的
Tell you what, save me a cold one.
地方不错啊
Nice place.
但是 要开始锁门了
You need to start locking your door, though.
什么都没打开
Everything's unpacked.
你们为我这么做的?
You did this all for me?
有些人需要承担责任
Someone needed to take responsibility.
我会给你们准备钥匙的 好吗?
I'm gonna get you all keys, alright?
伙计们
Guys...
嘿
Hey...
Hey.
好吧 猛男 如果我这么做你做什么
Okay, tough guy. What would you do if I did this...
不错啊
Not bad.
像丛林猫一样
It's the reflexes of a jungle cat.
是吗?
Is that right?
- 是的 - 是吗
- Yeah... - Yeah?
嘿
Hey.
嗨
Hi.
我还记得他刚穿上警服是瘦弱的样子
I can still see that skinny kid in his uniform.
总觉得不合适
Never really fit him.
我们都不合适
Didn't fit any of us.
他想要的就是抓住坏蛋
All he wanted was to catch the bad guy.
我本应该看出来的
I should've seen it.
你看出来了 是我逼的
You did. I pushed.
是我让你的
I let you.
你担心这样的事会发生在你身上吗?
You ever worry it'll happen to you?
每一天
Every day.